Guide to the Fritz Reiner papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Compact Disks
  - Mozart. A Musical Joke (Box 2, Folder 0054)
  - Falla, Manuel de. Nights in the Gardens of Spain (Box 2, Folder 0054)
  - Schumann. Symphony No. 2 in C (Box 2, Folder 0055)
  - Wagner. Parsifal (Box 2, Folder 0056)
  - Bach. Concerto for Two Violins (Box 2, Folder 0056)
  - Mozart. Symphony No. 41 (Box 2, Folder 0056)
  - Strauss. Der Rosenkavalier (Box 2, Folder 0056)
  - Busoni, Ferruccio. Turandot Suite (Box 2, Folder 0056)
  - Commentary by various associates including Joseph Szigeti and Rudolph Ganz. A BBC Program on Busoni (Box 2, Folder 0056)
  - Brahms. Symphony No. 2 (Box 2, Folder 0057)
  - Brahms. Variations on a Theme by Haydn (Box 2, Folder 0057)
  - Berlioz. Roman Carnival (Box 2, Folder 0069)
  - Strauss. Also Sprach Zarathustra (Box 2, Folder 0069)
  - Rogers, Richard. Carousel Waltz (Box 2, Folder 0069)
  - Beethoven. Concerto No. 5 (Box 2, Folder 0069)
  - Rogers, Richard. Carousel Waltz (Box 2, Folder 0069)
  - Prokofiev. Symphony No. 5 (Box 2, Folder 0069)
  - Interviewed by Edward Downes. Fritz Reiner Remembered--A Tribute on the Occasion of Reiner's 85th Birthday (Box 2, Folder 0069)
  - Berg, Alban. Violin Concerto (Box 3, Folder 0071)
  - Berg, Alban. Wozzeck (Box 3, Folder 0071)
  - Mussorgsky (orch. By Ravel). Pictures from an Exhibition (Box 3, Folder 0071)
  - Copland, Aaron. Quiet City (Box 3, Folder 0071)
  - Barber, Samuel. Symphony No. 2, Op. 19 (Box 3, Folder 0071)
  - Strauss. Till Eulenspiegel's Merry Pranks (Box 3, Folder 0071)
  - Wagner. Siegfried Idyll (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Haydn. Symphony No. 94 (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Vivaldi. Spring and Autumn (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Haydn. Symphony No. 101 (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Berlioz. Romeo and Juliet (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Welper/Berlioz. Invitation to the Dance (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Berlioz. Symphonie Fantastique (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Hindemith. Cello Concerto (Box 3, Folder 0072)
  - Beethoven. Symphony No. 4 (Box 3, Folder 0073)
  - Hindemith. Violin Concerto (Box 3, Folder 0074)
  - Hindemith. Cello Concerto (Box 3, Folder 0074)
  - Mussorgsky. Khovanchina (Box 3, Folder 0074)
  - Strauss. Four Songs (Vier Lieder) (Box 3, Folder 0074)
  - Strauss. Salome (Box 3, Folder 0074)
  - Tcherepnin, Nikolay. Divertimento, Op. 90 (Box 3, Folder 0075)
  - Bartok. The Miraculous Mandarin Suite (Box 3, Folder 0075)
  - Bach. St. Anne (Box 3, Folder 0076)
  - Debussy. La Mer (Box 3, Folder 0076)
  - Sibelius. Finlandia (Box 3, Folder 0076)
  - Sibelius. Symphony No. 5 (Box 3, Folder 0076)
  - Tcherepnin, Nikolay. Divertimento, Op. 90 (Box 3, Folder 0077)
  - Wagner. Lohengrin (Box 3, Folder 0077)
  - Wagner. Tannhauser (Box 3, Folder 0077)
  - Mendelssohn. Wedding March (Box 3, Folder 0077)
  - Brahms. Symphony No. 2 in D, Op. 73 (Box 3, Folder 0078)
  - Brahms. Variations on a Theme by Haydn (Box 3, Folder 0078)
  - Franck. Le Chausser Maudit (Box 3, Folder 0079)
  - Schumann. Cello Concerto (Box 3, Folder 0079)
  - Verdi. Requiem (Box 3, Folder 0079)
  - Mahler, Gustav. Symphony No. 94 (Box 3, Folder 0079)
  - Beethoven. Symphony No. 4 (Box 3, Folder 0080)
  - Schoenberg, Arnold. Verklarte Nacht (Box 3, Folder 0080)
  - Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich. Kamarinskaya (Box 3, Folder 0080)
  - Humperdinck, Engelbert. Hansel und Gretel (Box 3, Folder 0080)
  - Wagner. Götterdämmerung (Box 3, Folder 0080)
  - Hindemith. Theme and Variations for Piano and Orchestra (Box 3, Folder 0081)
  - Kodály, Zoltán. Dances from Galanta (Box 3, Folder 0081)
  - McBride, Robert. Swing Stuff (Box 3, Folder 0081)
  - Milhaud, Darius. Concerto for Two Pianos and Orchestra (Box 3, Folder 0081)
  - Casella, Alfredo. Paganiniana (Box 3, Folder 0081.)
  - Rossini. Il Signor Bruschino (Box 3, Folder 0081)
  - Rachmaninof Rhapsody on a Theme of Paganini, Op. 43 (Box 3, Folder 0081)
  - Mozart. Bassoon Concerto in Bb, K. 191 (Box 3, Folder 0082)
  - Mozart. Serenade No. 9 in D, K. 320 (Posthorn) (Box 3, Folder 0082)
  - Smith/Key. The Star Spangled Banner (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Berlioz. Roman Carnival (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Debussy. Iberia (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Falla, Manuel de. El Amor Brujo (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Ravel. Daphnis et Chloe Suite (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Strauss. Salome (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Strauss. Domestic Symphony (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Mussorgsky. Boris Godunov (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Debussy. Petite Suite (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Bartok. Two Hugarian Dances (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Ravel. Le tombeau de Couperin (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Strauss. Till Eulenspiegel's Merry Pranks (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Weber, Carl Maria von. Euryanthe (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Mozart. Symphony No. 40 in G Minor (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Schumann. Sideshow for Orchestra (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Bartok. Hungarian Sketches (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Mozart. The Impresario Overture (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Mussorgsky. Night on Bald Mountain (Box 3, Folder 0083)
  - Wagner. Lohengrin (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Donato. Sinfonietta No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Haydn. Sinfonia Concertante in Bb, Op. 84 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Satie. Gymnopedies, Nos. 1 and 3 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Ravel. La Valse (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Tchaikovsky. March from Suite No. 3 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Debussy. Two Nocturnes: Nuages and Fêtes (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Saint-Saens. Cello Concerto in A, Op. 33 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Berlioz. Beatrice and Benedict Overture (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Beethoven. Symphony No. 8 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Tchaikovsky. Piano Concerto No. 1 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Mahler, Gustav. Das Lied von der Erde (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Kodály, Zoltán. Peacock Variations (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Bartok. The Miraculous Mandarin Suite (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Brahms. Symphony No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 0084)
  - Mozart. Serenade No. 9 in D, K. 320 (Posthorn) (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Mozart. Bassoon Concerto (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Mozart. Le Nozze di Figaro (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Wagner. Lohengrin (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Wagner. Lohengrin (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Wagner. Die Walküre (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Wagner. Siegfried (Box 3, Folder 0085)
  - Prokofiev. Symphony No. 5, Op. 100 (Box 3, Folder 0086)
  - Kodály, Zoltán. Peacock Variations (Box 3, Folder 0087)
  - Bartok. The Miraculous Mandarin Suite (Box 3, Folder 0087)
  - Mendelssohn. Capriccio for Piano and Orchestra (Box 3, Folder 0087)
  - Roussel, Albert. Bacchus et Ariane Suite, No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 0087)
  - Wagner. Parsifal (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Delius, Frederick. A Dance Rhapsody No. 1 (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Elgar, Sir Edward. Introduction and Allegro (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Haydn. Symphony No. 3 (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Mozart. Symphony No. 41 (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Thomson, Virgil. Symphony No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Rossini. La Gazza Ladra (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Thomas, Ambroise. Mignon (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Smetana, Bed?ich. The Bartered Bride (Prodana nev?sta (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Strauss. Voices of Spring (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Bizet. L'Arlesienne Suite (Box 3, Folder 0088)
  - Wagner. Tristan and Isolde (Box 3, Folder 0089)
  - Wagner. Die Fliegende Hollander (Box 3, Folder 0089)
  - Wagner. Die Walküre (Box 3, Folder 0090)
  - Strauss. Der Rosenkavalier (Box 4, Folder 0091)
  - Wagner. Die Walküre (Box 4, Folder 0091)
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 4, Folder 0092)
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 4, Folder 0093 (1))
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 4, Folder 0093 (2))
  - Glazunov, Aleksandr. Scenes de Ballet (Box 4, Folder 0093 (2))
  - Sibelius. Symphony No. 6 in B, Op. 53 (Box 4, Folder 0093 (2))
  - Schubert. Symphony No. 7 in C (Box 4, Folder 0094)
  - Bach. Brandenburg Concertos (Box 4, Folder 0094)
  - Strauss. Don Juan (Box 4, Folder 0095)
  - Strauss. Also Sprach Zarathustra (Box 4, Folder 0095)
  - Verdi. Requiem (Box 4, Folder 0095)
  - Liebermann, Rol Concerto for Jazz Band and Symphony Orchestra (Box 4, Folder 0096)
  - Strauss. Don Juan (Box 4, Folder 0096)
  - Shostakovich. Symphony No. 6, Op. 53 (Box 4, Folder 0097)
  - Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich. Kamarinskaya (Box 4, Folder 0097)
  - Wagner. Tannhauser (Box 4, Folder 0097)
  - Rogers, Richard. Carousel Waltz (Box 4, Folder 0097)
  - Rachmaninof Isle of the Dead (Box 4, Folder 0097)
  - Liszt. Totentanz (Box 4, Folder 0097)
  - Liszt. Mephisto Walz (Box 4, Folder 0097)
  - Mahler, Gustav. Songs of a Wayfarer (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Strauss. Salome (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Gershwin/Bennett. Porgy and Bess-A Symphonic Picture (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Strauss. Don Juan (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Ravel. La Valse (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Ravel/Debussy. Danse (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Beethoven. Symphony No. 2 in D, Op. 36 (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Shostakovich. Symphony No. 6, Op. 53 (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Bach. Suite No. 2 in b for Flute and Strings (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Bach. Fugue in G minor (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Debussy. Iberia (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Berlioz. Hungarian March (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Rogers, Richard. Carousel Waltz (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Falla, Manuel de. El Amor Brujo (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Strauss. Gypsy Baron: Treasure Waltz (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Mussorgsky. Night on Bald Mountain (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Kabalevsky, Dmitry Borisovich. Colas Breugnon (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Wagner. Parsifal (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Debussy. Prelude to The Afternoon of a Faun (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Debussy. Two Nocturnes: Nuages and Fêtes (Box 4, Folder 0098)
  - Schumann. Symphony No. 1 (Spring) (Box 4, Folder 0099)
  - Glazunov, Aleksandr. Scenes de Ballet (Box 4, Folder 0099)
  - Strauss. Der Rosenkavalier (Box 4, Folder 0099)
  - Mozart. Le Nozze di Figaro (Box 4, Folder 0099)
  - Monteverdi, Claudio. Orfeo ed Euridice (Box 4, Folder 0099)
  - Bizet. Carmen (Box 4, Folder 0099)
  - Mozart. Serenade No. 9 in D, K. 320 (Posthorn) (Box 4, Folder U01)
  - Mozart. Bassoon Concerto, K. 191 (Box 4, Folder U01)
  - Brahms. Variations on a Theme by Haydn (Box 4, Folder U01)
  - Beethoven. Symphony No. 8 (Box 4, Folder U01)
  - Haydn. Symphony No. 95 (Box 4, Folder U01)
  - Bach/Stock. Prelude and Fugue in Eb (Box 4, Folder U02)
  - Debussy. La Mer (Box 4, Folder U02)
  - Interview by Steven Temmer during Intermission (Box 4, Folder U02)
  - Sibelius. Finlandia (Box 4, Folder U02)
  - Sibelius. Symphony No. 5 (Box 4, Folder U02)
  - Auber, Daniel-François-Esprit. Masaniello (Box 4, Folder U03)
  - Copland, Aaron. The Tenderland Suite (Box 4, Folder U03)
  - Ravel. La Valse (Box 4, Folder U03)
  - Beethoven. Symphony No. 8 (Box 4, Folder U03)
  - Bartok. The Miraculous Mandarin Suite (Box 4, Folder U03)
  - Riegger, Wallingford. New Dance (Box 4, Folder U03)
  - Strauss. Der Rosenkavalier (Box 4, Folder U04)
  - Wagner. Die Walküre (Box 4, Folder U04)
  - Copland, Aaron. Concerto for Clarinet and Orchestra (Box 4, Folder U04)
  - Brahms. Symphony No. 2 (Box 4, Folder U04)
  - Brahms. Academic Festival Overture (Box 4, Folder U04)
  - Rubenstein, Anton. Concerto in d Minor for Piano and Orchestra (Box 4, Folder U04)
  - Hofmann. Chromaticon, Duologue for Piano and Orchestra (Box 4, Folder U04)
  - Haydn. Symphony No. 101 (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Haydn. Symphony No. 94 (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Weber/Berlioz. Invitation to the Dance (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Berlioz. Symphonie Fantastique (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Berlioz. Romeo and Juliet (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Saint-Saens. Symphony No. 3 (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Mendelssohn. Meeresstille und glückliche Fahrt (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - WQXR. Listening Room. Chicago Symphony Members discuss Reiner (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Interview by Edward Donnes (Box 4, Folder U05)
  - Bartok. Divertimento for Strings (Box 4, Folder U06)
  - Brahms. Piano Concerto No. 1 (Box 4, Folder U06)
  - Debussy. Prelude to The Afternoon of a Faun (Box 4, Folder U06)
  - Debussy. Two Nocturnes: Nuages and Fêtes (Box 4, Folder U06)
  - Wagner. Parsifal (Box 4, Folder U06)
  - Wagner. Die Meistersinger (Box 4, Folder U06)
  - Tchaikovsky. Serenade for Strings (Box 4, Folder U06)
  - Strauss. Der Rosenkavalier (Box 4, Folder U07)
  - Conversation between Reiner and Stephen Temmer (Box 5, Folder U08)
  - Sibelius. Finlandia (Box 5, Folder U08)
  - Sibelius. Symphony No. 5 in E-Flat Major, Op. 82 (Box 5, Folder U08)
  - Mussorgsky. Khovanchina (Box 5, Folder U08)
  - Mussorgsky. Pictures from an Exhibition (Box 5, Folder U08)
  - Brahms. Symphony No. 3 (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Brahms. Violin Concerto (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Auber, Daniel-François-Esprit. Masaniello (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Copland, Aaron. The Tenderland Suite (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Mozart. Concerto for Two Pianos in E-Flat, K. 365 (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Bach/Cailliet. Fugue in G minor (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Beethoven. Concerto No. 4 (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Vaughan-Williams. Fantasia on a Theme by Thomas Tallis (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Wagner. A Faust Overture (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Eppert. Speed, Op. 53 (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Strauss. Till Eulenspiegel's Merry Pranks (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Bartok. Divertimento for Strings (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Bartok. Concerto No. 3 (Box 5, Folder U09)
  - Holst, Gustav. Suite from The Perfect Fool (Box 5, Folder 010)
  - Symphony No. 4 in D minor (Box 5, Folder 010)
  - Wagner. Die Götterdämmerung (Box 5, Folder 010)
  - Hindemith. Cello Concerto (Box 5, Folder 010)
  - Ravel. Daphnis et Chloe (Box 5, Folder 010)
  - Ravel. Tzigane (Box 5, Folder 010)
  - Shuller, Gunther. Spectra (Box 5, Folder U11)
  - Mahler, Gustav. Symphony No. 101 (Box 5, Folder U11)
  - Bartok. Piano Concerto No. 1 (Box 5, Folder U11)
  - Bartok. The Miraculous Mandarin Suite (Box 5, Folder U11)
  - Prokofiev. Symphony No. 5 (Box 5, Folder U12)
  - Brahms. Symphony No. 3 (Box 5, Folder U12)
  - Mozart. Le Nozze di Figaro (Box 5, Folder U13 (1))
  - Mozart. Le Nozze di Figaro (Box 5, Folder U13 (2))
  - Kodály, Zoltán. Peacock Variations (Box 5, Folder U14)
  - Bartok. The Miraculous Mandarin Suite (Box 5, Folder U14)
  - Brahms. Symphony No. 2 (Box 5, Folder U14)
  - Strauss. Salome (Box 5, Folder U14)
  - Auber, Daniel-François-Esprit. Masaniello (Box 5, Folder U14)
  - Copland, Aaron. The Tenderland Suite (Box 5, Folder U14)
  - Mozart. Concerto for Two Pianos in E-Flat, K. 365 (Box 5, Folder U14)
  - Tchaikovsky. Symphony No. 4 (Box 5, Folder U15)
  - Berlioz. Roman Carnival (Box 5, Folder U15)
  - Saint-Saens. Symphony No. 3 (Box 5, Folder U16)
  - Mendelssohn. Meeresstille und glückliche Fahrt (Box 5, Folder U16)
  - Rogers, Richard. Carousel Waltz (Box 5, Folder U16)
  - Beethoven. Leonore No. 3 (Box 5, Folder U16)
  - Debussy. La Mer (Box 5, Folder U16)
  - Stravinsky. Le Sacre du Printemps (Box 5, Folder U16)
  - Smith/Key. The Star Spangled Banner (Box 5, Folder U16)
  - Schubert. Symphony No. 9 (Box 5, Folder U17)
  - Handel. Messiah (Box 5, Folder U17)